Guide to the Brooklyn, N.Y., Department of Law, Corporation Counsel records 2013.015
Brooklyn Historical Society
- Series 1: Case Files, 1849-1920; 98.0 linear feet; in 199 manuscripts boxes, 4 flat boxes and 1 flat file drawer
  - Krakower, Henry - Board of Health violation, 1901 (Box 151, Folder 14)
    35 Graham Ave.
  - Kreidemacher, Philip - 241 Palmetto St. and 375 Hamburg Ave. sewer property damage, 1901 (Box 151, Folder 15)
  - Lennon, James - Kings County Sheriff dispute, 1901- 1902 (Box 151, Folder 16)
  - Levanion, John F. - Fireman salary, 1901 (Box 151, Folder 17)
  - Lovelace, Mary - South 9th St. sidewalk injury, 1901 (Box 151, Folder 18)
  - Luongo, Frank - 14 St. Edwards St. sewer property damage, 1901-1903 (Box 151, Folder 19)
  - Lyons, Catherine A. - Assessment dispute, 1901 (Box 151, Folder 20)
    Pennsylvania Ave. assessment; Ward ? - Block 274 - Lots 16- 17
  - MacDaniel, William R. - Brooklyn Disciplinary Training School for Boys foreman printer salary, 1901 (Box 151, Folder 21)
  - Maier, John G. - 96 Eldert St. sewer property damage, 1901-1904 (Box 151, Folder 22)
  - Mail and Express Company, 1901 (Box 151, Folder 23)
  - Manahan, James J. - 170 Woodbine St. sewer property damage, 1901 (Box 151, Folder 24)
  - Mangold, August - 1346 Gates Ave. sewer property damage, 1901 (Box 151, Folder 25)
  - Marlow, Elizabeth, 1901 (Box 151, Folder 26)
  - Martin, Charles S. and Louis J. Schussler - Coney Island Pier assessment, 1901 (Box 152, Folder 1)
    Ocean Navigation and Pier Company
  - McArdle, Terence - Street Sweeper appointment, 1901 (Box 152, Folder 2)
    Veteran employment
  - McCann, Thomas - Prospect Ave. nuisance, 1901- 1902 (Box 152, Folder 3)
  - McCanna, Patrick - Department of Public Charities salary, 1901 (Box 152, Folder 4)
  - McCoy, Elizabeth and Edward Jentz - 222 and 246 Palmetto St. sewer property damage, 1901 (Box 152, Folder 5)
  - McElroy, Annie - 8th St. bicycle injury, 1901 (Box 152, Folder 6)
  - McKinnon, Elizabeth - 64 Adelphi St. sidewalk injury, 1901- 1902 (Box 152, Folder 7)
  - McNamara, Charles - Water supply contract, 1901 (Box 152, Folder 8)
    Citizen's Water Supply Company
  - Meehan, James - County jail discharge, 1901 (Box 152, Folder 9)
  - Messerschmidt, Frederick - 343 Knickerbocker Ave. sewer property damage, 1901 (Box 152, Folder 10)
  - Meyer, John - County jail discharge, 1901 (Box 152, Folder 11)
  - Minto, Sarah C. and Robert F. - 874 to 892 Jefferson Ave. improper building construction, 1901 (Box 152, Folder 12)
  - Moeller, Henry - Emmons Ave. opening assessment, 1901 (Box 152, Folder 13)
  - Molitor, William E. - Brooklyn Disciplinary Training School for Boys caretaker salary, 1901-1902 (Box 152, Folder 14)
    Or Moliter
  - Moran, Fannie - Boerum Pl. sidewalk injury, 1901 (Box 152, Folder 15)
  - Munez, Elizabeth - Tax surplus, 1901 (Box 152, Folder 16)
    Ward 29 - Block 103 (?) - Lots 10-11
  - Murray, Douglas - Fireman salary, 1901 (Box 152, Folder 17)
  - Murray, Sanford, 1901 (Box 152, Folder 18)
  - Nazry, Annie B. - 415 Warren St. sewer property damage, 1901- 1903 (Box 152, Folder 19)
  - Nolan, William - Ash and rubbish dumping, 1901 (Box 152, Folder 20)
  - O'Connell, Joseph J. - Expert witness on mental diseases, 1901 (Box 152, Folder 21)
  - O'Connor, Thomas - Department of Water Supply inspector salary, 1901-1902 (Box 152, Folder 22)
  - O'Donnell, James J. - 405 Warren St. sewer property damage, 1901-1903 (Box 152, Folder 23)
  - O'Keefe, Michael - Fireman salary, 1901 (Box 152, Folder 24)
  - Olson, Oswald - County jail discharge, 1901 (Box 152, Folder 25)
  - Osterman, Aaron - Assessment dispute, 1901 (Box 152, Folder 26)
    Ward 29 - Block 54 - Lots 9-14 (Northeast corner of Gravesend Ave. (now McDonald Ave.) and Vanderbilt St.)
  - Oswald, Henry - County jail discharge, 1901 (Box 152, Folder 27)
  - Pell, William J. and others - Foreclosure, 1901 (Box 152, Folder 28)
    164 South 5th St.
  - Peoples Trust Company, as executor of Michael W. Wall - Assessment dispute, 1901-1902 (Box 152, Folder 29)
    Several properties around White St., Varet St., and Siegel St.; Includes action against Eliza A. Wall, as executor of William Wall, and others
  - Petroski, Michael - County jail discharge, 1901 (Box 153, Folder 1)
    Or Petriski; Tacia Koaso?
  - Pfeiffer, Louis - County jail discharge, 1901 (Box 153, Folder 2)
  - Post, Philip - Water inspector dismissal, 1901 (Box 153, Folder 3)
    Includes civil service rulebook
  - Power, Maurice - County jail discharge, 1901 (Box 153, Folder 4)
  - Prospect Land and Improvement Company - Assessment dispute, 1901 (Box 153, Folder 5)
    Ward 30 - Block 893 - Lot 35 (Block bound by 6th Ave., 71st St., 72nd St., and Stewart Ave.)
  - Richardson, James A. - Patchen Ave. wagon injury, 1901 (Box 153, Folder 6)
  - Robertson, Lily - 11 St. Edwards St. sewer property damage, 1901-1903 (Box 153, Folder 7)
  - Rogers, Sarah - 418 Warren St. sewer property damage, 1901-1903 (Box 153, Folder 8)
  - Rogers, William - County jail discharge, 1901 (Box 153, Folder 9)
  - St. Philip's Church - Assessment dispute, 1903 (Box 153, Folder 10)
    11th Ave. and 80th St.
  - Sample, Annie against Frank and Joseph Sample - Non-support of mother, 1901 (Box 153, Folder 11)
  - Schiavoni, Gracia against John F. Harriot, 1901 (Box 153, Folder 12)
  - Schlitz, Henry and John - Pauper burials, 1901 (Box 153, Folder 13)
  - Schmidt, Ernestine - 244 Palmetto St. sewer property damage, 1901 (Box 153, Folder 14)
  - Schmidt, Henry - Bay 13th St. wagon injury, 1901 (Box 153, Folder 15)
  - Schmidtt, George C. and others, as the executors of Charles N. Krick - Emmons Ave. opening assessment, 1901 (Box 153, Folder 16)
  - Schroeder, Catharine against Mary E. Lynch and others - Foreclosure, 1901 (Box 153, Folder 17)
    North 6th St. and Wythe Ave.
  - Schuebert, Henrietta, 1901 (Box 153, Folder 18)
  - Seaboard Telegraph and Telephone Company - License dispute, 1901 (Box 153, Folder 19)
  - Seamens Bank for Savings in the City of New York against James Burke and others - Foreclosure, 1901 (Box 153, Folder 20)
    362 Clinton Ave. and 109 Greene Ave.
  - Sears, Sarah A. - Humboldt St. sewer property damage, 1901 (Box 153, Folder 21)
  - Schuh, George J. against the Brooklyn Heights Railroad Company and the City of New York, 1901 (Box 153, Folder 22)
  - Signar, Frank - County jail discharge, 1901 (Box 153, Folder 23)
  - Sloan, Joe - County jail discharge, 1901 (Box 153, Folder 24)
  - Smith, Thomas D. - Baisley's pumping station farm property damage, 1901-1906 (Box 153, Folder 25)
  - Snowman, George and Lydia - Humboldt St. and Nassau Ave. sewer property damage, 1901 (Box 153, Folder 26)
  - Steinhilber, John - Rent for election purposes, 1901 (Box 153, Folder 27)
  - Stern, William H., 1901 (Box 153, Folder 28)
  - Stewart, S. E. (?), as executor of Mannie W. Stewart - Surf Ave. assessment, 1901 (Box 153, Folder 29)
  - Stoll, Robert against Augustus Peverelly, 1901 (Box 153, Folder 30)
  - Story, Joseph S. - Assessment dispute, 1901 (Box 153, Folder 31)
    Ward 29 - Block 128 - Lot 4 (Block bound by Gravesend Ave. (now McDonald Ave.), Avenue C, Avenue D (now Cortelyou Rd.), and West St. (now Dahill Rd.))
  - Stuart, Alfred J. - Fire Department engineer salary, 1901 (Box 153, Folder 32)
  - Sumwalt, Charles H. against Morris Adler and John J. Morrissey, 1901-1903 (Box 153, Folder 33)
  - Sutton, Belle Stow - Assessment dispute, 1901 (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - Thompson, George - County jail discharge, 1901 (Box 154, Folder 2)
  - Tobin, Margaret, widow of John J. Tobin - Fireman pension, 1901 (Box 154, Folder 3)
  - U. S. Standard Voting Machine Company against the Board of Elections, 1901 (Box 154, Folder 4)
  - Van Orden, De Ruyter against William H. Allen - Unearned trial fee, 1901 (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - Van Sicklen, James and Abraham - Queens County pumping stations property damage, 1901-1903 (Box 154, Folder 6)
    Or Van Siclen; Lincoln Ave.
  - Vanderveer, George W. and Hugh Goodwin, as executors of William Vanderveer - Surf Ave. assessment, 1901-1902 (Box 154, Folder 7)
  - Von Hillebrandt, Adolphine, as administratrix of Oscar Von Hillebrandt - Teacher salary, 1901 (Box 154, Folder 8)
  - Werckmeister, Conrad - 13 St. Edwards St. sewer property damage, 1901-1903 (Box 154, Folder 9)
  - Wilkes, Daniel W. - Street sprinkling services, 1901 (Box 154, Folder 10)
  - Wilson, William - Assessment dispute, 1901 (Box 154, Folder 11)
    Ward 30 - Block 564 - Lots 2-5 (8th Ave., between 72nd St. and 73rd St.)
  - Worsley, Henry, 1901 (Box 154, Folder 12)
  - Ahearn, Jeremiah H., 1902 (Box 154, Folder 13)
  - Almirall, R. F. - Library plans and specifications, 1902 (Box 154, Folder 14)
    For the Avon Hall (Bedford) branch
  - Andrews, Missouri - Duffield St. injury, 1902 (Box 154, Folder 15)
  - Bates, Mary - 776 Bedford Ave. injury, 1902 (Box 154, Folder 16)
  - Beardall, John - Prospect Ave. assessment, 1902 (Box 154, Folder 17)
  - Beniston, William - 1329 Greene Ave. sewer property damage, 1902 (Box 154, Folder 18)
  - Bishop, Frederick H. - Sewer property damage, 1902 (Box 154, Folder 19)
    See also complaints of Elise Kellerman, Herman Kellerman, and Catherine Kilcoyne
  - Blau, Frank M. - 744 Coney Island Ave. rent for election, 1902-1903 (Box 154, Folder 20)
  - Boardman, William L. - Prospect Ave. assessment refund, 1902 (Box 154, Folder 21)
  - Bohanan, John - Surf Ave. assessment, 1902 (Box 154, Folder 22)
  - Brooklyn Guild Association - 245 Concord St. sewer property damage, 1902 (Box 154, Folder 23)
  - Brooklyn Heights Railroad Company - Pavement repair, 1902 (Box 154, Folder 24)
    Flatbush Ave., between Malbone St. and Fort Hamilton Ave.
  - Brown, Charles A. and John Fleming - County of Richmond contract, 1902 (Box 154, Folder 25)
  - Buschmann, Albert D. - Surf Ave. assessment, 1902 (Box 154, Folder 26)
  - Bush Company, Limited - 43rd St. bulkhead obstruction, 1902 (Box 154, Folder 27)
  - Carey, Isaac H. and William Wolff, 1902 (Box 154, Folder 28)
  - Carney, Peter B. - Fireman dismissal, 1902-1903 (Box 154, Folder 29)
  - Carvey (?), Margaret - 13th St. sidewalk injury, 1902 (Box 238, Folder -)
    Survey of 13th St., east of 3rd Ave.
  - Catholic Women's Association - Assessment dispute, 1902 (Box 154, Folder 30)
    10 Prospect Pl.
  - Clare, Dennis J. - Clerk salary, 1902 (Box 154, Folder 31)
  - Clark, Caroline A. - Release of City's interest in a portion of the old Brooklyn, Flatbush and Jamaica Turnpike, 1902 (Box 154, Folder 32)
    11th Ward
  - Cody, Elizabeth L. and Charles Hart - Shore Rd. construction services (1 of 2), 1902-1904 (Box 154, Folder 33)
    Includes specifications for Shore Road
  - Cody, Elizabeth L. and Charles Hart - Shore Rd. construction services (2 of 2), 1902-1904 (Box 155, Folder 1)
  - Cohen, Samuel - Harrison Pl. wagon injury, 1902 (Box 155, Folder 2)
  - Cook, John A. - Surf Ave. assessment, 1902 (Box 155, Folder 3)
  - Cranford, Walter V. - Paving contract dispute (1 of 3), 1902 (Box 155, Folder 4)
  - Cranford, Walter V. - Paving contract dispute (2 of 3), 1902 (Box 155, Folder 5)
  - Cranford, Walter V. - Paving contract dispute (3 of 3), 1902 (Box 155, Folder 6)
  - Cranford Company against City of New York and James Jennings, 1902 (Box 155, Folder 7)
  - Danaif, George M. - 128 Osborn St. injury (1 of 2), 1902 (Box 156, Folder 1)
  - Danaif, George M. - 128 Osborn St. injury (2 of 2), 1902 (Box 239, Folder -)
    Plan of 128 Osborn St.
  - Davis, B. H. - Assessment adjustment, 1902 (Box 156, Folder 2)
    Ward 30 - Block 29 - Lots 46-49 (65th St., between 14th Ave. and New Utrecht Ave.)
  - Dockter, Michael - 108 Broadway sewer property damage, 1902 (Box 156, Folder 3)
  - Donato, Tony against James V. Cunningham, the City of New York and others, 1902 (Box 156, Folder 4)
  - Dowling, William and John Kiernan - Assessment dispute, 1902 (Box 156, Folder 5)
    Ward 29 - Block 83 - Lot 9 (East 5th St., between Greenwood Ave. and Fort Hamilton Ave.)
  - Driggs, Edmund F., circa 1902 (Box 156, Folder 6)
  - Durnagl, Mathias - Personal injury, 1902 (Box 156, Folder 7)
  - Ellis, Garrett - Salary claim, 1902 (Box 156, Folder 8)
  - Ernst, Conrad - Chauncey St. wagon accident, 1902-1905 (Box 156, Folder 9)
  - Ewer, Peter F. - Foreclosure, 1902 (Box 156, Folder 10)
  - Feigenbaum, Bessie - Recovery of property, 1902 (Box 156, Folder 11)
  - Flanagan, Mary E. - Wagon accident death, 1902 (Box 156, Folder 12)
    Houston St. and Goerck St., Manhattan
  - Foster, Amaziah - Property damage, 1902 (Box 156, Folder 13)
  - Fox, Catharine L. - Assessment refund, 1902 (Box 156, Folder 14)
    Prospect Ave. assessment
  - Frohne, Ernest A. H. and Amelia - 682 and 694 Humboldt St. sewer property damage, 1902 (Box 156, Folder 15)
  - Galvin, James - 39th St. sidewalk injury, 1902 (Box 156, Folder 16)
  - Garlichs, Henry - 1233 Flushing Ave. sewer property damage, 1902-1904 (Box 156, Folder 17)
  - Garvey, Daniel S. - Patrolman dismissal, 1902-1905 (Box 156, Folder 18)
  - Gillen, James H. and John O'Brien - Police detective salaries (1 of 2), 1902-1904 (Box 156, Folder 19)
  - Gillen, James H. and John O'Brien - Police detective salaries (2 of 2), 1902-1904 (Box 156, Folder 20)
  - Glennon, Timothy C. - Brooklyn Disciplinary Training School for Boys teacher suspension, 1902-1905 (Box 157, Folder 1)
  - Gorden, Mary A. - Assessment dispute, 1902 (Box 157, Folder 2)
  - Haimer, Edwin A. - Prospect Ave. assessment refund, 1902 (Box 157, Folder 3)
  - Hamilton H. Salmon and Company - North Henry St. and Russell St. property damage, 1902 (Box 157, Folder 4)
  - Hann, John and George W. Phillips, 1902 (Box 157, Folder 5)
    Or Hahn
  - Hastings Pavement Company - Bay Ridge Parkway paving, 1902 (Box 157, Folder 6)
  - Hegeman, Charles, 1902 (Box 157, Folder 7)
  - Hettich, Joseph, 1902 (Box 157, Folder 8)
  - Higbie, Joseph S. - Property damage, 1902 (Box 157, Folder 9)
  - Hill, James, Jr. - School janitor services, 1902 (Box 157, Folder 10)
  - Hoff, S. Adelia, 1902 (Box 157, Folder 11)
  - Hoffman, George and Samuel Zorn, 1902 (Box 157, Folder 12)
  - Hopfensack, Annie - Award for properties on Leonard St., McKibbin St., and Boerum St., 1902 (Box 157, Folder 13)
  - Jamaica Savings Bank, 1902 (Box 157, Folder 14)
  - Jenkins, Charles H. - Republican primary election, 1902 (Box 157, Folder 15)
  - Johnson, Frederick - Assessment refund, 1902 (Box 157, Folder 16)
    Ward 29 - Block 127 - Lots 76-79 (East 9th St., between Avenue C and Courtelyou Rd.)
  - Johnson, Walter E. - Carpenter services, 1902 (Box 157, Folder 17)
  - Kane, William F. - Brooklyn Disciplinary Training School for Boys dismissal, 1902 (Box 157, Folder 18)
  - Kelly, James T. - Assessment dispute, 1902 (Box 157, Folder 19)
    Ward 29 - Block 87 - Lots 12 and 48 (Prospect Ave., between Greenwood Ave. and Ocean Parkway)
  - Kramat, Edward - 153 57th St. wagon injury, 1902 (Box 157, Folder 20)
  - Leach, Martin - 338 Metropolitan Ave. injury, 1902 (Box 157, Folder 21)
  - MacMonnies, Frederick, 1902 (Box 157, Folder 22)
  - Martens, Hoag, and Company - Telegraph wire horse injury, 1902 (Box 157, Folder 23)
  - Massa, Antonio - Assessment cancellation, 1902 (Box 157, Folder 24)
    Surf Ave. assessment
  - McClean, Joseph F. and Teresa V. Ennis against Edward J. McLaughlin and Edwin N. Furman, and the City of New York - Mortgage dispute, 1902 (Box 157, Folder 25)
    West 17th St. and Coney Island Creek
  - McDonald, Mary - 84, 86 and 92 Diamond St. sewer property damage, 1902 (Box 157, Folder 26)
  - Mooney, George Walton - Personal injury, 1902 (Box 157, Folder 27)
  - Nassau County Electric Railroad Company against Long Island Railroad Company and others (1 of 2), 1902 (Box 157, Folder 28)
    Regarding tracks at the junction of Atlantic Ave. and Flatbush Ave.
  - Nassau County Electric Railroad Company against Long Island Railroad Company and others (2 of 2), 1902 (Box 158, Folder 1)
  - O'Brien, Mary - 104 Warren St. injury, 1902-1918 (Box 158, Folder 2)
  - O'Brien, Sarah and Timothy - 229 Walworth St. injury, 1902 (Box 158, Folder 3)
  - O'Keeffe, Michael - Deputy Collector of Assessments and Arrears dismissal, 1902 (Box 158, Folder 4)
  - Oliver, Ann E. - Award for property acquired to open West 16th St., 1902 (Box 158, Folder 5)
  - O'Rourke, John - Sewer assessment cancellation, 1902 (Box 158, Folder 6)
    Ward 29 - Block 350 - Lots 5-6 (Fenimore St., between Nostrand Ave. and New York Ave.)
  - Page, Edwin F. - Clerk salary, 1902 (Box 158, Folder 7)
  - Prehn, Frederick - Assessment refund, 1902 (Box 158, Folder 8)
    Ward 29 - Block 68 - Lots 9-10 (Southwest corner of Vanderbilt St. and Prospect Ave.)
  - Price, Edith Y. - Coal deliveries to pumping stations (1 of 4), 1902-1904 (Box 158, Folder 9)
  - Price, Edith Y. - Coal deliveries to pumping stations (2 of 4), 1902-1904 (Box 158, Folder 10)
  - Price, Edith Y. - Coal deliveries to pumping stations (3 of 4), 1902-1904 (Box 159, Folder 1)
  - Price, Edith Y. - Coal deliveries to pumping stations (4 of 4), 1902-1904 (Box 159, Folder 2)
  - Property Owners' Association of Arverne- by-the-Sea - Return of cart, 1902 (Box 159, Folder 3)
  - Pullman, John - 741 Union St. obstruction, circa 1902 (Box 159, Folder 4)
  - Quinn, William P. - 238 South 5th St. property acquisition award, 1902 (Box 159, Folder 5)
  - Roberts, Jason - Prospect Ave. assessment, 1902 (Box 159, Folder 6)
  - Rogers, Susan - Personal injuries, 1902 (Box 159, Folder 7)
  - Rooney, Daisy B. - 56 St. Johns Pl. injury, 1902 (Box 159, Folder 8)
  - Ryan, Matthew P. - Removing encumbrances, 1902 (Box 159, Folder 9)
  - Saxton, Mary - 1370 Herkimer St. sidewalk injury, 1902 (Box 159, Folder 10)
  - Scheidt, John H., Henry Strubbe and John Ward - Surf Ave. assessment disputes, 1902 (Box 159, Folder 11)
  - Shealor, Lizzie E., 1902 (Box 159, Folder 12)
  - Sheepsheads Bay Methodist Episcopal Church - Assessment dispute, 1902 (Box 159, Folder 13)
  - Sigretto and Mannino - Sewer construction, 1902 (Box 159, Folder 14)
  - Slocum, Louis W. - Tax sale cancellation, 1902 (Box 159, Folder 15)
    Ward 7 - Block 57 - Lot 45 (Block bound by Greene Ave., Clifton Pl., Downing Ave., and Irving Pl.)
  - Smith, Clarence B. - Assessment cancellation, 1902 (Box 159, Folder 16)
    Ward 24 - Block 129 - Lot 50 (Dean St., between Albany Ave. and Troy Ave.)
  - Smith, Bridget A. and others - Assessment dispute, 1902 (Box 159, Folder 17)
    Ward 14 - Block 33 - Lot 45 (North 8th St., between Wythe Ave. and Berry St.)
  - Sposato, Carmine - Long Island farm damage, 1902 (Box 159, Folder 18)
  - Stacom, Catherine and Michael - Henry St. crosswalk injury (1 of 2), 1902-1906 (Box 159, Folder 19)
  - Stacom, Catherine and Michael - Henry St. crosswalk injury (2 of 2), 1902-1906 (Box 238, Folder -)
    Plan showing a crosswalk of Union and Henry Sts.
  - Stamm (?), Louisa - Randall's Island Hospital nurse services, 1902 (Box 159, Folder 20)
  - Swasey, Lewis M. - Assistant clerk salary, 1902 (Box 159, Folder 21)
  - Taylor, N. Phillips - Williamsburg tax sales, 1902 (Box 159, Folder 22)
  - Thornton N. Motley Company - Department of Water Supply materials, 1902 (Box 159, Folder 23)
  - Title Guarantee and Trust Company - Duryea property, 1902 (Box 159, Folder 24)
    Ocean Parkway assessment
  - Title Guarantee and Trust Company - Tax sale dispute, 1902 (Box 159, Folder 25)
  - Van Ness, Emma, as administratrix of Harry E. Tice, 1902 (Box 159, Folder 26)
  - Warren, Dorman T. - Assessment dispute, 1902 (Box 159, Folder 27)
    Ward 30 - Block 1050 - Lot 5 (Block bound by Ridge Blvd., 81st St., 82nd St., and 3rd Ave.)
  - Walter, Philipena - Rockville Centre property damage, 1902 (Box 159, Folder 28)
  - Weedon, Elizabeth - Foreclosure, 1902 (Box 159, Folder 29)
  - Weiner, Isaac N. - Use of premises in the former Town of Flatbush, 1902 (Box 159, Folder 30)
  - Weisbecker, Bernard and Henry Koch - 48 Morrell St. unsafe building, 1902 (Box 159, Folder 31)
  - Whitlock, Thomas C. - Counsel fees, 1902 (Box 159, Folder 32)
  - Wuest, Otto, Francis J. Rourke, and Benjamin P. Benjamin - Notary fees, 1902 (Box 159, Folder 33)
  - Young, Mary, 1902 (Box 160, Folder 1)
  - Zeiner, Edward J. A., 1902 (Box 160, Folder 2)
  - A. P. Smith Manufacturing Company - Department of Water Supply services, 1903 (Box 160, Folder 3)
  - Ahern, Charles, 1903 (Box 160, Folder 4)
  - Baranowski, Thomas - 349 Knickerbocker Ave. sewer property damage, 1903-1905 (Box 160, Folder 5)
  - Barringarten, Louise - 92 1/2 and 94 Guernsey St. sewer property damage, 1903-1904 (Box 160, Folder 6)
  - Beagan, Owen, 1903 (Box 160, Folder 7)
  - Bergsteen, A. O. - 88a 4th Ave. sewer property damage, 1903 (Box 160, Folder 8)
  - Blackman, Elizabeth M. againt Frank H. Bush and others - Foreclosure, 1903 (Box 160, Folder 9)
    Ward 22 - Block 106 - Lot 76 (10th St., between 4th Ave. and 5th Ave.)
  - Bockus, John - 173 Carlton Ave. sidewalk injury, 1903-1905 (Box 160, Folder 10)
  - Brady, John - Corona, Queens injury, 1903 (Box 160, Folder 11)
  - Bremer, John P., 1903 (Box 160, Folder 12)
  - Brennan, Patrick, 1903 (Box 160, Folder 13)
  - Bribben, Emeline C. - 314 Halsey St. sewer property damage, 1903 (Box 160, Folder 14)
  - Briggs, R. V. - 104 4th Ave. sewer property damage, 1903 (Box 160, Folder 15)
  - Brooklyn Heights Railroad Company - Test of the Poulson plan on the Brooklyn Bridge, 1903 (Box 160, Folder 16)
  - Brouck, J. - 108 4th Ave. sewer property damage, 1903 (Box 160, Folder 17)
  - Burke, Amelia - 281a Halsey St. sewer property damage, 1903-1904 (Box 160, Folder 18)
  - Burnes, Vincent A. - County jail discharge, 1903 (Box 160, Folder 19)
  - Busby, William - West 17th St. horse and surrey accident, 1903-1906 (Box 160, Folder 20)
    Includes Catherine Clough injury claim
  - Byrne, Margaret - 402 and 404 Warren St. sewer property damage, 1903 (Box 160, Folder 21)
  - Cavanagh, Victor F. - Assessment dispute, 1903 (Box 160, Folder 22)
  - Chappel, Robert against Gustav Lindenthal (Commissioner of Bridges), 1903 (Box 160, Folder 23)
  - Childs, A. E. - West 5th St. opening assessment, 1903 (Box 160, Folder 24)
  - Churchill, Margaret, 1903 (Box 160, Folder 25)
  - Clark, Morgan - 611 Evergreen Ave. sewer property damage, 1903-1905 (Box 160, Folder 26)
  - Clement, James N. - 84 Diamond St. sewer property damage, 1903 (Box 160, Folder 27)
  - Cobb, George W., Jr. against Daniel J. Ryan - Lien, 1903 (Box 160, Folder 28)
  - Collins, Patrick - 756 Macon St. sewer property damage, 1903 (Box 160, Folder 29)
  - Coney Island Fire Department, 1903 (Box 160, Folder 30)
  - Conklin, Hannah J. - Deed application, 1903 (Box 160, Folder 31)
    Ward 26 - Block 239 - Lot 11; formerly Hannah J. Angell
  - Conlon, Charles A. - Assessment cancellation, 1903 (Box 160, Folder 32)
    Ward 31 (all): Block 97 - Lots 1-2 (East 16th St., bewteen Avenue M and Avenue N); Block 195 - Lot 1 (Avenue O, between East 8th St. and East 9th St.)
  - Craigie, Mary E. - Brooklyn Public Library director reinstatement (1 of 4), 1903-1906 (Box 160, Folder 33)
  - Craigie, Mary E. - Brooklyn Public Library director reinstatement (2 of 4), 1903-1906 (Box 161, Folder 1)
  - Craigie, Mary E. - Brooklyn Public Library director reinstatement (3 of 4), 1903-1906 (Box 161, Folder 2)
  - Craigie, Mary E. - Brooklyn Public Library director reinstatement (4 of 4), 1903-1906 (Box 161, Folder 3)
  - Cronin, Hannah - Sidewalk injury, 1903 (Box 161, Folder 4)
  - Crouse, Kenneth H. - Claim of costs, 1903 (Box 161, Folder 5)
  - Cunningham, Orville - County jail discharge, 1903 (Box 161, Folder 6)
  - Curran, Ann - 393 Warren St. sewer property damage, 1903 (Box 161, Folder 7)
  - Curry, David, 1903 (Box 161, Folder 8)
  - Damm, George - 446 Knickerbocker Ave. sewer property damage, 1903-1905 (Box 161, Folder 9)